Bob Considine Papers
Bob Considine Papers
- Published materials
  - Articles by others
    - Smith, Charlotte Hale, "Seven Children in Seven Months…Plus 400 More," Atlanta Journal and Constitution Magazine, 1970 (Box 100)
    - Various authors, regarding law in the Soviet Union, 1959-1960 (Box 100)
    - Unknown author, "Air Lines Set Pace for Industry", 1933; chapter 3 from Aircraft Yearbook (Box 100)
    - Unknown author, "North American Aviation, Inc.," Aero Digest, Feb 1934 (Box 100)
    - Unknown author, "The Physical Fitness Index", undated (Box 100)
    - Miscellaneous photocopied articles on aviation, 1941-1944 (Box 100)
  - Booklets by Considine
    - 13 excerpts (with pictures) from Dempsey by the Man Himself, as told to Bob Considine and Bill Slocum (Box 100)
    - 17 Lives, 1956; published by Mutual Benefit Health & Accident Association; photos in book match some in the photographs section of this collection; 2 copies (Box 100)
    - The Great A-Bomb Robbery, 1951-1952; reprinted by Carbide and Carbon Chemical Co.; 2 copies (Box 100)
    - How Russia is Winning the Peace...Uncensored, by William Randolph Hearst Jr. with Considine and Frank Conniff, 1958; published by Hearst Corp.; 2 copies (Box 100)
    - How Russia Stole America's Atomic Secrets, 1951; 2 copies (Box 100)
    - Your Newspaper, 1954-1955; 3 copies (Box 100)
    - Your Newspaper Fights for Your Right to Know, 1956; 2 copies (Box 100)
  - Booklets by others
    - Anderson, Ragnar H., The Greater Rockford: Off for Stockholm, 1928; Return 1969, Apr 1971; reprinted from The Swedish Pioneer Quarterly (Box 100)
    - Brooks, Jerome E., The America's Cup, Thomas J. Lipton Inc., 1958 (Box 100)
    - Dubach, Harold W. and Taber, Robert W., Questions About the Oceans, National Oceanographic Data Center, 1969 (Box 100)
    - Dupree, O. C., 1957; rejected stories; also includes a loose manuscript, Dr. Jekyll and Miss Hyde (Box 101)
    - Hall, Floyd D., Sunrise at Eastern: Re-Birth of a Pioneer Airline, Newcomen Society, 1965 (Box 101)
    - Harrison, Emma, Public Welfare, Public Affairs Committee, 1963 (Box 101)
    - Hearst, William Randolph Jr., Report on Russia...uncensored, Hearst Corporation, 1955 (Box 101)
    - Hoyt, Waite, Babe Ruth as I Knew Him. Dell Publishing Co., 1948 (Box 101)
    - Kilgallen, James L., It's a Great Life: My 50 years as a Newspaperman, 1956; 2 copies (Box 101)
    - Reay, Thomas M., The Fantastic Story of the 'Hiking Viking' Bert R.J. 'Fish' Hassell, H.C. Johnson Press, undated (Box 101)
    - Schisgall, Oscar, The Enemy Property Issue, Public Affairs Committee, 1957 (Box 101)
    - Shurcliff, William A., SST and Sonic Boom Handbook, Citizens League Against the Sonic Boom, 1969 (Box 101)
    - Simmons, Gene, On the Moon with Apollo 15: A Guidebook to Hadley Rille and the Apennine Mountains, NASA, 1971 (Box 101)
    - Skutt, V. J., Mutual of Omaha The Good Neighbor, Newcomen Society, 1961 (Box 101)
    - Sullivan, Patrick M., Sportsline: A Television and Radio Production of Quizball, a Game Simulating a Baseball or Football Match, self-published, 1957 (Box 101)
    - Taylor, Eugene J., Help at Last for Cerebral Palsy, Public Affairs Committee, 1950 (Box 101)
    - Wainwright, Nicolas B., The History of the Philadelphia Inquirer, 16 Sep 1962; supplement to The Philadelphia Inquirer (Oversize 7)
    - Various authors, 2nd Annual Global World Series of Baseball Souvenir Book, Sep 1956 (Oversize 7)
    - Various authors, Dateline: 1776. Journalism in the United States, the First 200 Years, Overseas Press Club of America, 1976 (Box 101)
    - Unknown author, Aeroflot 71 Illustrated Review, Aeroflot, 1971 (Box 101)
    - Unknown author, The American Heritage World War II Chronology, American Heritage Publishing Co., 1966 (Box 101)
    - Unknown author, Apollo 15 July 26, 1971 Flight Plan Final, NASA (Box 101)
    - Unknown author, Apollo-Soyuz Astronyms, Aeronutronic Ford Corp., undated (Box 101)
    - Unknown author, Bronx Veterans Administration Hospital, Four Chaplains' Memorial Swimming Pool Dedication Journal, 1947 (Oversize 7)
    - Unknown author, A Holdra És a Rajta Túl Lévö Világokba [Hungarian booklet about Apollo 11 mission] (Oversize 7)
    - Unknown author, America House, America Development Office, undated (Oversize 7)
    - Unknown author, How to Avoid Libel, undated (Box 101)
    - Unknown author, In Regard to the News… Time, Inc., 1957 (Box 101)
    - Unknown author, Man on the Moon, a Picture Chronology of Man in Space Exploration, Gallina Inc., 1969 (Box 101)
    - Unknown author, Marymount School 1026-1028 Fifth Avenue, New York, undated (Box 101)
    - Unknown author, The Productive Years, Age 45-65, National Association of Manufacturers, [1961?] (Box 101)
    - Unknown author, A Profile of Occidental and the Men Who Manage it, Occidental Petroleum Corp., undated (Box 101)
    - Unknown author, Redwing in Retrospect, Joint Task Force Seven Headquarters, 1956; commemorative booklet of the 17 nuclear tests done in the Pacific Ocean; includes mention and photo of Considine (Box 101)
    - Unknown author, The Sovereign Military Order of Malta, Yesterday and Today, undated (Box 101)
    - Unknown author, Spacecraft with Wheels, the Lunar Roving Vehicle, NASA and Boeing, undated (Box 101)
    - Unknown author, The Story of Alcock & Brown, City of Manchester [England] Airport Committee, 1969 (Box 101)
    - Unknown author, Think a Moment About Money...Your Money, Mutual of Omaha, undated (Box 101)
    - Unknown author, The U.S. Navy, Lockheed S-3A, Carrier-based ASW for the 70's, Lockheed California, 1971 (Box 101)
  - Books by Considine
    - Dempsey by the Man Himself (as told to Bob Considine and Bill Slocum), Simon and Schuster, 1960; Transferred to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
    - It's All News to Me, Meredith Press, 1967; Transferred to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
    - It's the Irish, Doubleday & Company, 1961; 2 copies; Transferred to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
    - The Men Who Robbed Brinks, the Inside Story of One of the Most Famous Holdups in the History of Crime (as told by Specs O'Keefe to Bob Considine), Random House, 1961; book jacket only (Box 102)
    - The Men Who Robbed Brinks, the Inside Story of One of the Most Famous Holdups in the History of Crime (as told by Specs O'Keefe to Bob Considine), Random House, 1961; published edition; Transferred to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
    - The Panama Canal [Bengali translation by Nurul Hoque, printed by City Library in Dacca], 1963; Transferred to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
    - The Remarkable Dr. Armand Hammer, Harper & Row, 1975; book jacket and advertisement (Box 102)
    - The Remarkable Dr. Armand Hammer, Harper & Row, 1975; published edition; Transferred to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
    - Thirty Seconds Over Tokyo (by Captain Ted W. Lawson, edited by Considine), Random House, 1953; Transferred to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
  - Books by others
    - Baer, Arthur "Bugs", The Family Album, Albert & Charles Roni, 1925 (Box 114)
    - Bishop, Jim, The Day Lincoln was Shot, Harper & Brothers, 1955; signed by the author (Box 114)
    - Garst, Robert E. (ed.), Style Book of the New York Times, New York Times Co., 1956 (Box 114)
    - Gettelson, Leonard, Official World Series Records. Complete Box Scores of All Games 1903-1973, The Sporting News (Box 114)
    - Graham, Frank and Hyman, Dick, Baseball Wit and Wisdom: Folklore of a National Pastime, David McKay Company, 1962 (Box 114)
    - Ingells, Douglas J., Tin Goose: the Fabulous Ford Trimotor, Aero Publishers, 1968; signed by the author (Box 114)
    - Jacobs, Frank, The Highly Unlikely Celebrity Cookbook, New American Library, 1964 (Box 114)
    - Kaufman, Louis; Fitzgerald, Barbara; Sewell, Tom, Moe Berg: Athlete, Scholar, Spy, Little Brown, 1974; signed dedication to Considine from Sewell and Kaufman (Box 114)
    - Knappman, Edward W. (ed.), Watergate and the White House. V.1: June 1972-July 1973: Facts on File (Box 114)
    - Newman, Edwin, Strictly Speaking: Will America be the Death of English?, Bobbs-Merrill, 1974 (Box 114)
    - Riabchikov, Evgeny, Russians in Space, Doubleday & Co., 1971 (Box 114)
    - Saunders, Doris E. (ed.), The Day They Marched, Johnson Publishing Co., 1963; Transferred to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
    - Saunders, Doris E., (ed.), The Kennedy Years and the Negro: A Photographic Record, Johnson Publishing Co., 1964; Transferred to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
    - Sparks, James C. Jr., Rescue From the Air and in Space, Dodd, Mead & Co., 1963; signed by the author (Box 114)
    - Schlafly, Phyllis, A Choice Not an Echo, Pere Marquette Press, 1964 (Box 114)
    - Shirley, Sylvia W., Gourmet Wizardry, self published, undated (Box 114)
    - Stephenson, J. L., Anyone Can Have a Great Vocabulary, Avon, undated (Box 114)
    - Various authors, The Armand hammer Collection, Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1971 (Box 114)
    - Various authors, A Girl to Remember [tributes to Louise Baer], [1951?]; Transferred to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate this item.
    - Various authors, Good News for Modern Man, American Bible Society, 1974 (Box 114)
    - Various authors, Impressionist and Post-Impressionist Paintings from the U.S.S.R., M. Knoedler and Co., 1973; 2 copies (Box 114)
  - Bulletins
    - Miscellaneous (Box 102)
    - Miscellaneous, oversize (Oversize 28)
  - Catalogs
    - Armand Hammer Collection [University of Southern California], 1965 (Box 102)
    - Harper [publisher], 1975 (Box 102)
    - Meredith Press Books, 1967 (Box 102)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 102)
  - Clippings
    - Clippings by Considine, 1935; 1944-1948 (Oversize 28)
    - Clippings by Considine, 1949-1950 (Oversize 1)
    - Clippings by Considine, 1951-1956 (Oversize 8)
    - Clippings by Considine, 1957-1959 (Oversize 9)
    - Clippings by Considine, 1960 (Oversize 10)
    - Clippings by Considine, 1961-1962 (Oversize 11)
    - Clippings by Considine, 1963-1964 (Oversize 12)
    - Clippings by Considine, 1965-1974 (Oversize 13)
    - Clippings by Considine, labeled as "Overflow", 1943-1948 Apr; 7 folders; originally in envelopes labeled "overflow"; most are "On the Line" but there are also magazine and other clippings (Box 103)
    - Clippings by Considine, labeled as "Overflow", 1948, May-Dec; 6 folders; originally in envelopes labeled "overflow"; most are "On the Line" but there are also magazine and other clippings (Box 104)
    - Clippings by Considine, labeled as "Overflow", 1949; 6 folders; originally in envelopes labeled "overflow"; most are "On the Line" but there are also magazine and other clippings (Box 105)
    - Clippings by Considine, labeled as "Overflow", 1950; undated; 6 folders; originally in envelopes labeled "overflow"; most are "On the Line" but there are also magazine and other clippings (Box 106)
    - Clippings by Considine, translations, 1948-1975; translations of Considine articles into Spanish, Japanese, and Dutch for foreign press (Oversize 13)
    - Clippings about Considine, 1949-1957; undated (Box 107)
    - Clippings about Considine, 1945-1976; undated; 5 folders (Oversize 14)
    - Clippings by and about others, 1919; 1946-1974,; undated; 3 folders (Oversize 15)
    - Clippings, negative proofs (Box 107)
  - Fliers (Box 107)
  - Fliers, oversize (Oversize 16)
  - Fundraising appeals (Box 107)
  - Magazines
    - Advertising Age, 15 Jan 1963; specially bound issue gifted to Considine by the publisher, G.D. Crain Jr. (Oversize 16)
    - Air Force, Jun 1958; Sep 1972 (Box 107)
    - Air Force and Space Digest, Sep 1959; Jan, Sep, Nov 1962;; Nov 1970 (Box 107)
    - Air Line Pilot, Nov 1970; Jan 1972 (Box 107)
    - American Way, Mar 1974; Oct 1975; 2 copies (Box 107)
    - Collier's, May-Jun, 1943; 4 issues (Oversize 16)
    - Dun's Review, Apr, Jul 1975 (Box 107)
    - Editor & Publisher, 18 Aug 1951; 18 Jul 1953;; 31 May 1958;; 7 Jun 1958; 2 copies (Box 108)
    - Editor & Publisher, 1957, May 18-Jun 1; stories about newspaper promotion highlighting Considine (Box 108)
    - Life, 8 Aug 1969; 29 Aug 1969 (Oversize 16)
    - Newsweek, Nov 10, 1952; June 2, 1958; 2 copies (Box 108)
    - Oxy Today, spring 1973; winter 1973 (Box 108)
    - Reader's Digest, Jan 1959; Dec 1974 (Box 108)
    - Shell Aviation News, 1956; 1964,; 1970; 6 issues (Box 108)
    - Space Log [TRW], winter 1964/65; fall 1965 (Box 108)
    - Space World, 1961 Apr, Jun, Oct, Nov; 1962 Jan (Box 108)
    - Time, Apr 30, 1951; June 2, 1958;; Feb 9, 1959 (Box 108)
    - Miscellaneous, A-C (Box 109)
    - Miscellaneous, H-M (Box 109)
    - Miscellaneous, N-Q (Box 109)
    - Miscellaneous, R-Y (Box 109)
    - Miscellaneous, oversize (Oversize 16)
  - Newsletters, 1948; 1958,; 1962,; 1975 (Oversize 14)
  - News releases
    - A, 1949-1964 (Box 109)
    - B, 1956-1963 (Box 109)
    - C, 1947-1964 (Box 110)
    - D-H, 1957-1964 (Box 110)
    - I-J, 1957-1963 (Box 110)
    - K, 1949-1963; 2 folders (Box 110)
    - L, 1953-1964 (Box 110)
    - M-Me, 1954-1964 (Box 110)
    - Me-Mu, 1954-1961 (Box 111)
    - Pa-Po, 1958-1966 (Box 111)
    - Pr-T, 1958-1966 (Box 111)
    - U-Y, 1946-1964 (Box 111)
  - Newspaper columns
    - On The Line clippings, 1935-1959; 10 folders (Oversize 17)
    - On The Line clippings, 1960-1962; 11 folders (Oversize 18)
    - On The Line clippings, 1963-1965; 11 folders (Oversize 19)
    - On The Line clippings, 1966-1971; 13 folders (Oversize 20)
    - On The Line clippings, 1972, Jan-Jun; 6 folders (Oversize 21)
    - On The Line clippings, 1972, Jul-Dec; 1974 Jan; 10 folders (Oversize 22)
    - On The Line clippings, 1974, Feb-Sep; 8 folders (Oversize 23)
    - On The Line clippings, 1974, Oct-Dec; 1975, Jan-Aug; 7 folders (Oversize 24)
    - On The Line clippings, 1975, Sep; undated; 4 folders (Oversize 25)
  - Pamphlets and brochures from others
    - New Family Center, Tokyo, circa 1953 (Box 112)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 112)
  - Promotional material
    - INS: The Story of International News Service, undated (Oversize 16)
    - International News Service, miscellaneous (Box 112)
    - King Features (Box 112)
    - On the Line (Oversize 16)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 112)
  - Programs, 1946; 1966,; undated (Box 112)
  - Proceedings of the Fourth Eurospace U.S. - European Conference, Venice, Sep 22-25, 1970 (Box 112)
- Recordings
  - Audiorecordings
    - A Time to Keep: 1964, Voices and events of the year... Narration by Chet Huntley and David Brinkley, considine_b_015; RCA Victor LP recording; accompanied by a note from Elliot Horne to Bob Considine; VinylDisc; running time 53:20 (Oversize 5)
      Side 1: Voices Of Protest Challenge The Old Disciplines; Sen. Barry Goldwater Enters The Presidential Race; Pope Paul VI Visits The Holy Land; Discotheque And The New Dance Crazes; Earthquake Devastates Alaska; Cassius Clay Defeats Sonny Liston; The Topless Bathing Suit; N. Y. World's Fair Opens; Mobs Riot In Cities In The North; President Signs The Civil Rights Bill; Sen. Goldwater Wins The California Primary; Goldwater Organizes Convention Drive; Republican Convention Highlights
      Side 2: The War In South Vietnam, Crisis In The Gulf Of Tonkin; Fighting In Cyprus And The Congo; Surprise U. S. Victory In The Olympics; Obituaries: Herbert Hoover, Gen. Douglas MacArthur, Eddie Cantor, Gracie Allen; The Warren Report On President Kennedy's Assassination; Jack Ruby Sentenced To Death; Democratic Convention Highlights; The Presidential Campaign And The Election; Soviet Premier Khrushchev "Resigns"; Red China Explodes Nuclear Bomb; Martin Luther King Wins Nobel Peace Prize; Court Officer Frees 21 In Deaths Of Three Civil Rights Workers; U. S. Scores Space Spectacular With Close-Up Moon Pictures, Fires Satellite Toward Mars
    - Address by Lt. General Maxwell D. Taylor, C. G. Eighth US Army, Korea, at United Nations (UN) and 8th Army PIO Conference, Seoul. Gen. Taylor then presents Legion of Merit to Col. R. P. Rosengren, PIO, 9 Mar 53; 23 December 1965; considine_b_024; accompanied by photocopy of the old tape box and a letter from Colonel R. P. Rosengren to Bob Considine; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 113)
    - Address by Reverend Theodore M. Hesburgh, C. S. C. New York Notre Dame President's Committee Dinner. Introduction by Mr. Harry Hagerty (part 1 and 2), November 10th, 1960; considine_b_017; Empire Broadcasting Corp. LP record; accompanied by Hesburgh's business card; VinylDisc (Oversize 5)
    - Ask me Anything, J. Savard and Art. Slattery, 10/6/60; considine_b_025; accompanied by an envelope from Arthur J. Slattery to Bob and old label; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 113)
    - Civil Air Patrol Testimonial: Public Service Spot Announcements, considine_b_001; VinylDisc (Oversize 5)
      Side 1 (one minute): 1. Joe E. Brown; 2. Bob Considine; 3. Bob Cummings; 4. Frank Gallup [sic]; 5. Arthur Godfrey; 6. Garry Moore; 7. Dick Powell; 8. James Stewart
      Side 2 (20 second): 1. Joe E. Brown; 2. Bob Considine; 3. Bob Cummings; 4. Arthur Godfrey; 5. Garry Moore; 6. Dick Powell; 7. James Stewart; 8. James Stewart (30 second)
    - Do Not Weep for Me, lyrics by M. Staton, music by Priscilla Stanton, 4-9-49; considine_b_020; Griffin LP recording; accompanied by old sleeve with handwritten notes from Margaret Staton to Mr. Considine; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 5)
    - Do Not Weep for Me, vocal by Johnny Craig, music by Priscilla Stanton, words by M. Staton, 4-21-49; considine_b_021; Griffin LP recording; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 5)
    - Elvis Sings: Return To Sender; Where Do You Come From, Oct 1962; considine_b_009; RCA Victor record with original sleeve; VinylDisc; running time 4:10 (Oversize 5)
      Side 1: Elvis Presley With The Jordanaires ?– Return To Sender (from the Paramount Picture "Girls! Girls! Girls!") (Otis Blackwell-Winfield Scott)
      Side 2: Where Do You Come From (from the Paramount Picture "Girls! Girls! Girls!") (Ruth Batchelor-Bob Roberts)
    - Faron Young: Backtrack; I Can't Find The Time, 1961; considine_b_011; Capitol Record with original sleeve; VinylDisc; running time 4:37 (Oversize 5)
      Side 1: Faron Young - Backtrack (Alex Zanetis-Faron Yong
      Side 2: Faron Young - I Can't Find The Time (Hank Cochran-Willie Nelson)
    - (How Can I Write On Paper) What I Feel In My Heart; Losing Your Love, 1961; considine_b_010; RCA Victor record; VinylDisc; running time 4:38 (Oversize 5)
      Side 1: (How Can I Write On Paper) What I Feel In My Heart, Jim Reeves (Carter-Harrison-Kent Reeves
      Side 2: Losing Your Love, Jim Reeves (Bill Anderson-Buddy Killen)
    - Leadership Is... Performed by Maritz Men and Maiden, 1971; considine_b_005; part of 21st Annual Sales Conference, Bermuda; in commemorative vinyl binder, with photographs, printed libretto, and clipping; VinylDisc (Box 16)
      Side A: Leadership Is People
      Side B: Leadership Is Change, Leadership Is You.
    - Love and Marriage; Love is a Many-Splendored Thing, 1955; considine_b_006; Columbia Promotion Record; VinylDisc; running time 5:5 (Oversize 5)
      Side 1: Love and Marriage, from the NBC-TV Producers Showcase "Our Town" - Cahn-Van Heusen - The Joe Loco Quintet
      Side 2: Love is a Many-Splendored Thing, sung in 20th Century-Fox Cinemascope Prod. "Love is a Many-Splendored Thing" - Webster-Fain - The Joe Loco Quintet
    - New York Dinner: Speakers Barbara Hubbard, Orville Freeman, David Clark, Rod Corney, Bob Hieronimus, Jean Houston, 4/2/74; considine_b_023; accompanied by photocopy of the old cassette box; 1/8 inch audio cassette; running time 60:00 (Box 113)
    - Old Time Melodies, Sisters of Providence, Sister Rose of Jesus at the Organ [copy 1], considine_b_018; Montana Centennial Memories LP record; VinylDisc (Oversize 5)
    - Old Time Melodies, Sisters of Providence, Sister Rose of Jesus at the Organ [copy 2], considine_b_019; Montana Centennial Memories LP record; VinylDisc (Oversize 5)
    - One Giant Step..., Neil Armstrong, 07/20/1969; considine_b_002; front cover: "That's one small step for a man, one giant leap for mankind," on back cover: "The Triumph and the Tragedy of a Decade of Devotion to an Impossible Dream"; VinylDisc (Oversize 5)
    - One Giant Step..., Neil Armstrong, 07/20/1969; 1970; considine_b_003; front cover: "That's one small step for a man, one giant leap for mankind," on back cover: "The Triumph and the Tragedy of a Decade of Devotion to an Impossible Dream"; VinylDisc (Oversize 5)
    - One Giant Step: The History in Sound of America's Man-In-Space Program, 1973; considine_b_014; Mutual Broadcasting System LP Album; narrated by Bob Considine; VinylDisc (Oversize 5)
    - Personal Power through Creative Selling, Elmer G. Leterman, World's Best-Known Insurance Salesman, 1961; considine_b_012; Success Motivation Institute LP record, with original sleeve and complete script of the narration.; VinylDisc (Oversize 5)
      Side 1: 1. An Introduction to Elmer Leterman; 2. Decide What You Want to do; 3. Salesmanship Is Work; 4. Know-How and Know-Yourself Turn Effort Into Profit; 5. Planning Is the Best Technique; 6. Magic Salesmanship
      Side 2: 1. Showmanship; 2. Love People; 3. Watch Your Head and Keep Growing; 4. Dare To Believe; 5. Are You ready for Today?
    - Rockets, Missiles and Space Travel, Written and Directed by Willy Ley, 1958; considine_b_016; VOX LP album, with original album sleeve.; VinylDisc (Oversize 5)
      Side 1: Count-Down And Take-Off Of An Atlas; Interview With General Yates; Interview With Colonel Stevens; Interview With Mr. B. G. MacNab; Interview With Capt. Griffith; Interview With Lt. Passi; Count-Down And Firing Of A Snark; Firing Of A Corporal; Firing Of An Honest John Rocket; Count-Down And Firing Of A Jupiter Missile
      Side 2: The Sound Of a V-2; Interview With Wernher Von Braun; Interview With General Dornberger; Interview With Krafft Ehricke; Interview With Colonel Stapp; Interview With Professor Cooper; Interview With General Schriever; Count-Down And Take-Off Of Jupiter-C
    - Seventieth Birthday Party, In Honor of Irving Geist, 06/21/1970; considine_b_004; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 5)
    - Something About Lee Wiley, on Bob Hope Presents the Chrysler Theatre, 11 Oct 1963; considine_b_007; RCA Victor record with original sleeve; VinylDisc (Oversize 5)
      Side 1: East of the Sun; Can't Get Out of This Mood, Lee Wiley with Ralph Burns and his Orchestra
      Side 2: (Got the) South in My Soul; Time on My Hands (You in My Arms), Leo Reisman and his Orchestra Lee Wiley, vocal
    - Stories Adapted From Classics Illustrated Magazine: Space Stories and Sounds, 1959; considine_b_013; Lion Records LP album of science fiction stories; VinylDisc (Oversize 5)
      "The First Men in the Moon" by H. G. Wells; "The War of the Worlds" by H. G. Wells; "The Time Machine" by H. G. Wells; "A Journey to the Center of the Earth" by Jules Verne narrated by Bill Stern. Music by Bill Simon, script adapted by Roberta Strauss from Classics Illustrated Magazine, narrated by Bill Stern. Album produced by Arthur Pine. Bill Simon, Organ, Herb Harris, Percussion, Walter Gustafson, Sound Effects.
    - The Twelve Days of Christmas; Ringo Bells, 1964; considine_b_008; ATCO record with original sleeve; VinylDisc; running time 4:56 (Oversize 5)
      Side 1: The Twelve Days of Christmas, (Trad. - Arr. Rufus Smith) Three Blonde Mice, Accompanied by The Rufus Smith Quintet; Ringo Bells (George T. Simon), Three Blonde Mice, Accompanied by The Rufus Smith Quintet